// list of all questions, answers, and correctAnswer
var questions = [
  {
    question: "Boolean operators that can be used in JavaScript include:",
    answers: [
      "'And' Operator &&",
      "'Or' Operator ||",
      "'Not' Operator !",
      "All the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All the above"
  },

  {
    question: "What is the data type of variables in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      "Object data types",
      "Function data type",
      "None of the above",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Object data types"
  },
  {
    question: "Which one is a looping structure in JavaScript?",
    answers: ["All the below", "For", "While", "do-while loops"],
    correctAnswer: "All the below"
  },
  {
    question: "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
    answers: ["quotes", "curly brackets", "parentheses", "square brackets"],
    correctAnswer: "parentheses"
  },
  {
    question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store ____.",
    answers: [
      "numbers and strings",
      "other arrays",
      "booleans",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of the above"
  },
  {
    question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
    answers: ["strings", "booleans", "alerts", "numbers"],
    correctAnswer: "alerts"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which one of these is not among the three different types of errors in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      "Animation time errors",
      "Load time errors",
      "Run time errors",
      "Logical Errors"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Animation time errors"
  },
  {
    question:
      "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
    answers: ["commas", "curly brackets", "quotes", "parentheses"],
    correctAnswer: "quotes"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the two basic groups of data types in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      "Primitive and attribute",
      "Primitive and reference types",
      "Reference types and attribute",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Primitive and reference types"
  },
  {
    question:
      "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
    answers: ["JavaScript", "terminal / bash", "for loops", "console.log"],
    correctAnswer: "console.log"
  }
];